msmobiles.com 2012-11-23

# WMPoweruser.com Privacy Policy | WMPoweruser

****Information about our Organisation and Web site****

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like WMPoweruser.com . We are based in UK. Our principal activity is: Providing Technology news and discussion forums. Our privacy policy covers WMPoweruser.com and its Web site:  
****Organisation Name:  
WMPoweruser.com

******Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

******The services and links of our Web site** ****

Our Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data.

Our Web site also includes a link to:

  * Google

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Such third party Web service providers may collect personal data about our visitors. ****Automatic Collection of Information

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.

We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.

****Data Collection and Purpose Specification

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations.

To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please [click here ](http://www2.oecd.org/#Table5_2)

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected

****Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.

We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by:

  * making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorised the collection of the child’s personal data and use of the child’s personal data for the disclosure to third parties.
  * giving parents the option to consent to the collection and use of the child’s personal data for our internal use and use of the child’s personal data for the disclosure to third parties.

We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data.

****Disclosure and Visitor Choice

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.

****Confidentiality / Security

We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data.

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

  * unauthorised access
  * improper use or disclosure
  * unauthorised modification
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data.

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

****Access to the personal data we may hold about you

You can ask us, by:

  * sending an email ( webmaster@wmpoweruser.com )

whether we are keeping personal data about you.Upon request, which you can indicate by:

  * sending an email ( webmaster@wmpoweruser.com )

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a week. – although we may before require proof of your identity -. We will provide the information without any charge.We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:

  * rectified or amended

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

#### About Surur 

Site Admin and Windows Phone enthusiast, he has been using Windows Mobile devices since before they were called PocketPC’s. He is currently sporting a Nokia Lumia 920.
